

Fatemeh Sharifi Najafabadi

graphic designer

Cantact

fatemehsharifinj@yahoo.com

+45 4221 0523

www.fatemeh3d.ir

in linkedin.com/in/fatemeh-sharifi/

Randers C 8900, Denmark

Tools and Softwares

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Premier Adobe After Effects Chaos V-Rey Autodesk 3ds Max Autodesk Revit Autodesk Maya Autodesk AutoCAD



Animation Skills

Storyboard Character Design Object Design Modeling Lighting **Texturing Environment Design** Rendering Mixing and Editing films



Graphic Skills

Poster Design Logo Design **Business Card** Design **Book Illustration** Illustration



Languages

English Danish Farsi









Summery

Creative and passionate graphic designer with a bachelor's degree in graphic design. More than twelve years of experiences in computer graphic, 3d animations, and visual art and have a solid understanding of modeling, texturing, lighting, rendering in 3d graphics with Autodesk 3ds Max and excellent knowledge of 2d graphic with Adobe creative suite especially Photoshop.

Have passed courses and got certificates related to 3d graphic design and easy to learn new software as needed. Relocated to Denmark in Feb 2015 with the ability to use Danish and English in the intermediate level and ready to get a full-time job.

Experience

Freelance Graphic Designer

2016-2019

- Skills: Character design, Poster design, Logo design.
- Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator.

Interior and Exterior Designer, Chakad 2014-2015

- Skills: Poster design, Interior and exterior design, Counseling design.
- Tools: Autodesk 3ds Max, Autodesk Revit, Autodesk AutoCAD, Chaos V-Rey, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop.

Animation Team Lead, Chakad

2009-2011

- Skills: Team Lead, 3d character design, Modeling, lighting, Rendering, 3d environment design, Poster design, storyboard, Mixing movies.
- Tools: Autodesk 3ds Max, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premier, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects.

Animation Designer, Ofogh

- Skills: Concept planning, 3d object designer, character design, texturing, book illustration, Modeling, 3d environment design and mixing movies.
- Tools: Autodesk 3ds Max, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Adobe Illustrator.

Certifications

 3D Interior Design 	2013-2013
 3D Animation Production 	2011-2011
 Advanced Techniques in 3ds Max 	2010-2010

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Design	2012-2014
 Associate's Degree in Computer Software 	2004-2007